Alan Senderovich

FRONT END DEVELOPER



Work experience

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR.

Neta / December 2021 - August 2022

- Development in React.js, Next.js, TypeScript.
- Testing with React Testing Library & Jest.
- Back-end bounded tasks using Nest.js.
- Component documentation with Storybook.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR.

BullTech | January 2021 - December 2021

- Development and maintenance of components with React.js Redux.
- Testing with Jest.
- Analytics with Amplitude y Segment.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER JR.

Cohete-Ecommerce specialists | June 2020 - March 2021

- Layout of Landings Pages (HTML5 and CSS with interactions in JavaScript).
- Maintenance and adjustments in Shopify sites.

Professional training

--Platzi Front-end / March 2020 present

- HTML 5
- CSS Sass, Less
- React.js.
- React Native
- Next.js.

• Nest.js.

• TypeScript.

- --Soy Henry Bootcamp
 FullStack developer JR
 December 2021 April 2022
 - React.js Redux
 - Node.js
 - Express
 - Sequelize
 - Postgres

Personal profile

Frontend React developer with 1+ year experience (2+ years developer experience) working with React and Next.js creating responsive user interfaces.

Handling backend/data interactions through Nest.js. Currently expanding my knowledge in React Native to acquire solid skills in mobile development.

Great ability to work in a team, in constant search for learning and professional development.

Contact info

- Buenos Aires, Argentina.
- alansenderovich@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/alan-senderovich/
- github.com/Alan-Senderovich

Tech skills

- HTML5, CSS3 [Bootstrap, Tailwind]
- React.js Redux
- React Native.
- Next.js
- Nest.js
- SASS, LESS.
- Git (GitHub).

Professional skills

- Intermediate English.
- Motivation for continuous learning.
- Teamwork.
- Resolving power.